SIGIT ARDIANSYAH

+6289635560011 | sigitardiansyah24@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/sgtardiansyah/

Depok, West Java

Junior Data Analyst with over 2 years of experience in data analysis, visualization, and processing within the event organizer industry. Proficient in using Excel, SQL (MySQL), and Power BI to develop dashboards and generate strategic insights. Possesses a basic programming background in Python, JavaScript, and Node.js for data cleaning and automation. A collaborative team player with strong communication skills and a passion for problem-solving.

Work Experiences

PT. Pamerindo Indonesia - Jakarta

Jul 2022 - Present

Database Specialist

PT Pamerindo Indonesia is the leading trade fair organiser in Indonesia, established with the sole purpose of organising specialised trade exhibitions for the Indonesian market

- Managed and updated master data for major annual events.
- Analyzed post-event visitor data using Excel and SQL to support decision-making.
- Created interactive dashboards and analytical reports using Power BI.
- · Developed Python scripts to automate data cleaning and preprocessing workflows.

PT. Pamerindo Indonesia - Jakarta

May 2021 - Aug 2021

Telemarketing

PT Pamerindo Indonesia is the leading trade fair organiser in Indonesia, established with the sole purpose of organising specialised trade exhibitions for the Indonesian market

- · Maintained and updated the customer database.
- · Cleaned and segmented data using Excel.
- Supported the promotion team by analyzing customer data.

PT. Bank Syariah Mandiri - Jakarta

Sep 2018 - Nov 2018

IT Support Intern

PT Bank Syariah Mandiri is a banking institution in Indonesia that aims to optimize the potential of Islamic finance and economy.

- · Performed troubleshooting for hardware and software issues and inputted data into internal systems.
- Compiled weekly reports using Excel and assisted IT team with technical documentation.

PT. Pangkal Multikarya - Jakarta

Mar 2017 - Jul 2018

Finance Staff

PT Pangkal Multikarya as one of the largest authorized distributors of YKK AP already has 33 years of experience in the field of aluminium installation.

- Handled administrative transactions and prepared financial reports using Excel.
- Supported payroll processing and daily financial documentation.

Education Level

Universitas Persada Indonesia YAI - Jakarta, Indonesia

Bachelor's of Information Technology, 3.06/4.00

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Certification (2020): Certificate Wordpress Ecommerce
- Data Analysis & Visualization: Microsoft Excel, SQL (MySQL), Power BI
- Basic Programming: Python, JavaScript, Node.is, PHP
- Web & E-Commerce: WordPress, E-Commerce
- IT Support & Software Tools: IT Support, Computer Troubleshooting, Microsoft Office
- Multimedia & Design: Adobe Premiere
- · Soft Skills: Communication, Problem-Solving, Leadership, Adaptability